<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="heading">Beatles Anthlogy Vol.1</string>
    <string name="text"><b>We also provide rental air compressors and genuine parts and service</b>
        Summit Sierra is rated to provide superior service for 8000 hours in most air compressor applications.
        In addition to the annual savings in electricity the new compressors provide Bodine with a more reliable supply
    Have you ever wanted to visit the Pocono <br></br><br></br> Well here is some information about this beautiful place.
        The Poconos has been a wonderful place to vacation for years. They have everything for that
        romantic getaway or a family vacation. The Poconos offers something for everyone.http://www.samtse.gov.bt/announcements
    In a normal day of teaching golf I walk back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.<br></br><br></br>
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need aIn a normal day of teaching golf I walk
        back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey,
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need  Summit Sierra is rated to
        provide superior service for 8000 hours in most air compressor applications.<br></br> <br></br>
        Summit Sierra is rated to provide superior service for 000 hours in most air compressor applications.
        In addition to the annual savings in electricity,the new compressors provide Bodine with a more reliable supply
    Have you ever wanted to visit the Poconos Well here is some information about this beautiful place.
        The Poconos has been a wonderful place to vacation for years. <br></br><br></br>They have everything for that
        romantic getaway or a family vacation. The Poconos offers something for everyone.
    In a normal day of teaching golf I walk back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need aIn a normal day of teaching golf I walk
        back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need<br></br> <br></br>
        In addition to the annual savings in electricity the new compressors provide Bodine with a more reliable supply
        Have you ever wanted to visit the Pocono Well here is some information about this beautiful place.
        The Poconos has been a wonderful place to vacation for years. They have everything for that
        romantic getaway or a family vacation. The Pocon offers something for everyone.
    In a normal day of teaching golf I walk back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need aIn a normal day of teaching golf I walk
            back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey<br></br> <Br></Br>
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need
        In a normal day of teaching golf I walk back and forth to the range numerous times. On this journey
        I usually watch the different variations people have when they swing the golf club.
        Some of the swings are quite good and others need</string>
</resources>